https://business.dcu.ie/privacy-policy/

Who we are
Our website address is: https://business.dcu.ie/
What personal data we collect and why we collect it
Comments
When visitors leave comments on the site we collect the data shown in the comments form, and also the visitor’s IP address and browser user agent string to help spam detection.
An anonymized string created from your email address (also called a hash) may be provided to the Gravatar service to see if you are using it. The Gravatar service privacy policy is available here: https://automattic.com/privacy/. After approval of your comment, your profile picture is visible to the public in the context of your comment.
Media
If you upload images to the website, you should avoid uploading images with embedded location data (EXIF GPS) included. Visitors to the website can download and extract any location data from images on the website.
Contact forms
Cookies
If you leave a comment on our site you may opt-in to saving your name, email address and website in cookies. These are for your convenience so that you do not have to fill in your details again when you leave another comment. These cookies will last for one year.
If you have an account and you log in to this site, we will set a temporary cookie to determine if your browser accepts cookies. This cookie contains no personal data and is discarded when you close your browser.
When you log in, we will also set up several cookies to save your login information and your screen display choices. Login cookies last for two days, and screen options cookies last for a year. If you select “Remember Me”, your login will persist for two weeks. If you log out of your account, the login cookies will be removed.
If you edit or publish an article, an additional cookie will be saved in your browser. This cookie includes no personal data and simply indicates the post ID of the article you just edited. It expires after 1 day.
Embedded content from other websites
Articles on this site may include embedded content (e.g. videos, images, articles, etc.). Embedded content from other websites behaves in the exact same way as if the visitor has visited the other website.
These websites may collect data about you, use cookies, embed additional third-party tracking, and monitor your interaction with that embedded content, including tracking your interaction with the embedded content if you have an account and are logged in to that website.
Analytics
Who we share your data with
How long we retain your data
If you leave a comment, the comment and its metadata are retained indefinitely. This is so we can recognize and approve any follow-up comments automatically instead of holding them in a moderation queue.
For users that register on our website (if any), we also store the personal information they provide in their user profile. All users can see, edit, or delete their personal information at any time (except they cannot change their username). Website administrators can also see and edit that information.
What rights you have over your data
If you have an account on this site, or have left comments, you can request to receive an exported file of the personal data we hold about you, including any data you have provided to us. You can also request that we erase any personal data we hold about you. This does not include any data we are obliged to keep for administrative, legal, or security purposes.
Where we send your data
Visitor comments may be checked through an automated spam detection service.
Your contact information
Additional information
How we protect your data
What data breach procedures we have in place
What third parties we receive data from
What automated decision making and/or profiling we do with user data
Industry regulatory disclosure requirements
Pages2020 Jobs Stimulus courses
30% Club Female Executive Scholarship
About Research DCU
Academic Staff
Accreditations and Ranking
Alumni
Alumni Scholarships: DCU Executive MBA and DCU Business School Full-Time Masters Programmes
Ambition to Scale 2020
Application Process
AstraZeneca – DCU Business School – Covid-19 Leadership Webinar
BDO
Bus Eireann
Business Insights
Career Prospects
Contact Us
Course Detail
Current Students
DCU Business School International Teaching Week
Fintech Insights
Gaelic Players Association/DCU Masters Scholarship Programme
Graduate Employability
Home
IAA GEOFFREY O’ BYRNE WHITE MEMORIAL SCHOLARSHIP
Industry Advisory Board
INI – Leadership Team Programme
INI – Leading Within a Group
INI Leadership & Talent Programme
Invest Northern Ireland – Ambition to Scale Programme 2018/2019
ISTAT Scholarships (Aviation)
John Thompson Scholarship
Leadership Development for Women
Leading Within a Group Programme 2020
Live Q&A
MSc in Business Administration
MSDM Induction Week 2019
News and Events
Next Generation Management
Oberstown Leadership Exploration & Development Programme 2019
Online Programmes
Online Programmes
Opportunities
for Enterprise
Our Mission And Vision
Our People
Our Programmes
Our Structure
MINT
MSc Business (Management)
MSc E-Commerce
MSc Management (Strategy)
MSc Work & Organisational Psychology
MSDM
News
Postgraduate
Research
Scholarships
Study at DCUBS
Timetable
SOCIAL CHANNELS
LATEST NEWSGlobal Family Business Expert Dr. Justin Craig to join DCU Executive Education09/12/2020 - 3:51 pmThe Greatest Thing since Sliced Bread? Food Sustainability, Innovation and Entrepreneurship come to life for MSc Insights and Innovation Students08/12/2020 - 3:44 pmDCU Business School Ranks in The Financial Times Top European Business Schools 202007/12/2020 - 7:56 amDCU Business School lead global research consortium in an effort to tackle the entrepreneurial gender divide03/12/2020 - 4:55 pmSITEMAPHome
Business Insights
About Us
Why DCU Business School
Our Structure
Our People
Our Mission And Vision
Industry Advisory Board
Accreditations and Ranking
Contact Us
NEED TO FIND OUT MORE?
DCU main website
DCU Student APPS
DCU Staff APPS
Disclaimer
Privacy Policy
Scroll to top
This site uses cookies. By continuing to browse the site, you are agreeing to our use of cookies.OKLearn moreCookie and Privacy Settings
How we use cookies
We may request cookies to be set on your device. We use cookies to let us know when you visit our websites, how you interact with us, to enrich your user experience, and to customize your relationship with our website.
Click on the different category headings to find out more. You can also change some of your preferences. Note that blocking some types of cookies may impact your experience on our websites and the services we are able to offer.
Essential Website Cookies
These cookies are strictly necessary to provide you with services available through our website and to use some of its features.
Because these cookies are strictly necessary to deliver the website, you cannot refuse them without impacting how our site functions. You can block or delete them by changing your browser settings and force blocking all cookies on this website.
Google Analytics Cookies
These cookies collect information that is used either in aggregate form to help us understand how our website is being used or how effective our marketing campaigns are, or to help us customize our website and application for you in order to enhance your experience.
If you do not want that we track your visist to our site you can disable tracking in your browser here: Click to enable/disable Google Analytics tracking.
Other external services
We also use different external services like Google Webfonts, Google Maps and external Video providers. Since these providers may collect personal data like your IP address we allow you to block them here. Please be aware that this might heavily reduce the functionality and appearance of our site. Changes will take effect once you reload the page.
Google Webfont Settings:
Click to enable/disable Google Webfonts.
Google Map Settings:
Click to enable/disable Google Maps.
Vimeo and Youtube video embeds:
Click to enable/disable video embeds.
Privacy Policy
You can read about our cookies and privacy settings in detail on our Privacy Policy Page.
Privacy Policy
Accept settingsHide notification onlyCheck to enable permanent hiding of message bar and refuse all cookies if you do not opt in. We need 2 cookies to store this setting. Otherwise you will be prompted again when opening a new browser window or new a tab.Click to enable/disable essential site cookies.
